Hi guys welcome back to my channel today we
will talk about ICICI Lord's share
you will see it has created a hammer pattern on the one day time frame
and today by
giving CC it has given confirmation for buying
if you will see this line which
is continuing it has crossed in 10 EM
we have said that if any share crosses its 10
EM then the bias starts getting activated somewhere in it
if you will see this share is up to 20 EM
also which bridges then
buying can come in it and it will be even more
amazing you will see its next move can be
almost from here this share can
go up to
1990, say this share can go up to 1990 from here
if it starts sustaining above this then
this share can show you the share price till 2030 from here
if you see then almost
from its high this
share is at 18 to 19 it has fallen so
somewhere in it  Now, there is an opportunity for buying as
well and this E Na Khai has
created a bottom here as well,
so there is a great opportunity for buying from here,
this share must be bought from here, please
like the video,
if you are new to our channel then
please subscribe to the channel.